(Sheldon:)You continue to underestimate me,
my good man.
(Leonard:)If you weren't happy with my presentation,
then maybe you should've given it with me.
As I've explained repeatedly, unlike you,
I don't need validation from lesser minds.
(Leonard:)- No offense.
- Really? So why did you come?
- Because I knew you'd screw this up.
- I didn't screw it up.
(Sheldon:)Oh, please. I admit,
that spherical-chicken joke was hilarious.
- Thank you.
- It was straight downhill from there.
(Leonard:)I've had enough of your condescension.
(Leonard:)Maybe I didn't go to college
when I was 11, like you.
(Leonard:)Maybe I got my doctorate at 24
instead of 16.
(Leonard:)But you are not the only person who
is smarter than everyone else in this room.
(Leonard:)No offense.
(Leonard:)And I am clearly not the only person
who is tormented by insecurity...
(Leonard:)...and has an ego
in need of constant validation.
- So you admit you're an egotist.
- Yes.
(Leonard:)My name is Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
I could never please my parents...
...so I need to get my self-esteem
from strangers.
But he's worse!
(Sheldon:)Okay, that is it.
(Penny:)Stop it.